# Adam Luzsi | Software Engineer | Resume

- Phone: +41766118318
- Email: adamluzsi@gmail.com
- GitHub
- RubyGems
- LinkedIn
- Link to my CV / Portfolio

# Summary

I'm Adam Luzsi, a Senior Software Engineer with extensive expertise in Go, Ruby, and other programming languages. My diverse career spans across industries such as finance, healthcare, and insurance, where I've provided effective software solutions to complex problems. An avid open-source contributor, I'm committed to maintainable development and continuous learning. Explore further for a detailed insight into my technical skills and professional achievements.

# Personal Projects (OSS)

- frameless: Anti-framework for helping to build architecture flexibility and improve system maintainability.
- rack-app: Minimalist ruby web framework to enable rapid API development with strong testing support.
- **testcase**: Testing Tooling for Go to support various classicist TDD testing idioms.
- toggler: Self-hosted feature flag and a release management service.
- My presentation from UK GopherConf about the misunderstood HR tool: Microservices Architecture

# **Key Skills**

#### Technical Skills

- Programming Proficiency: Go, Ruby, C#, JavaScript/TypeScript, Java, PHP
- API Integration: Experience with RESTful, GraphQL, gRPC, SOAP, etc.
- Data Management Expertise:
  - Systems: PostgreSQL, MySQL, BoltDB, MongoDB, Redshift, Green-Plum, Redis, Kafka
  - PostgreSQL Specialist: Expertise in database management and optimization, Data Warehouse Engineering with Greenplum
- DevOps Experience:
  - On-call duties, tracing (e.g., OpenTelemetry), metric collection, automation

- Hosting on AWS, GCP, DigitalOcean, Heroku, on-premise
- Tooling: Terraform, Ansible, Docker, Helm, Kubernetes, Jenkins, ArgoCD
- Software Development Principles: 12-factor methodology, SOLID principles, Hexagonal architecture, Clean Architecture

#### Project and People Management Skills

- Project Management Methodologies: XP, Kanban, Scrum, Agile Development techniques
- Mentorship and Knowledge Sharing:
  - Team member growth
  - Open-source community contributions
  - Passion for knowledge sharing and guidance

## Industry Knowledge

- Industry Experience:
  - Finance, Marketing, Second-hand Marketplace, Healthcare, Insurance
- Payment Systems Development:
  - Designed and implemented enhancements to existing payment systems
  - optimized routing processes to reduce costs, utilizing intelligent algorithms
- Acquiring Registration System Development:
  - Responsible for the development and management of acquiring registration systems, including registration to acquiring-hosts and preparation of payment terminals.
- Marketing Automation Knowledge:
  - Employed various marketing automation tools and strategies to help marketing agents optimize campaigns reach targeted audiences, and increase engagement.
- Data Warehouse Management:
  - Extensive experience in designing, developing, and maintaining distributed database warehouses.
  - experience with data segmentation, analysis, and reporting
- User Behaviour Tracking:
  - Specialized in leveraging diverse methods for tracking user behavior, facilitating efficient ad targeting and collection of user impressions for strategic marketing efforts.

#### **Key Focus Areas**

- Maintainable Software Development
- Open-Source Contribution
- Continuous Learning

# Professional Experience

#### Senior Software Engineer | Teya / SaltPay | 2022 - 2023

- Played a key role in enhancing payment systems and decreasing costs through smart routing of the payments
- Took part of the development of company's the acquiring registration system. (registering to acquiring hosts, preparing terminals for payments, etc)

## Senior Software Engineer | Tutti / Tamedia / Swiss Marketplace Group | 2019 - 2022

- Improved user experience and streamlined transactions in a second-hand marketplace.
- Extended the payment system by integrating a new payment option, leading to a substantial increase in revenue.

#### Senior Software Engineer | Cembra Money Bank | 2018 - 2019

 Owned and led the replacement project of the ZEK integration system, leading to increased efficiency and continuous recognition from management.

#### Software Engineer | Emarsys-Technologies Kft | 2014 - 2018

- Key contributor to the design and building of scalable solutions for storing and analyzing big data.
- Maintained Ruby and Golang client libraries, reducing integration time from a week to just minutes.
- Significantly contributed to the creation of a tool that transforms raw data into valuable insights for strategic marketing and business growth.

#### Software Engineer | VeryCreatives Consultant | 2014 - 2016

- Designed a data aggregation ETL processing stack
- Held training on Agile practices, including topics such as the important of team communication through test automation.

#### Software Engineer | People Process Technologies | 2011 - 2014

- Led the design and implementation of a workflow engine which increased integrations and facilitated acquisition of new government projects.
- Spearheaded the design and implementation of an internal payment handling system, which was adopted by the Hungarian Government for managing employee benefits.

#### Open-Source Contributor | 2011 - Present

• Contributions to open-source projects along sharing my owns such as Frameless, Rack-App, Testcase, and Toggler.

• Regularly providing mentorship and sharing knowledge within the open-source community.

# Software Development Intern | CFB Kft | 2009 - 2011

• Participated in the design of compliant insurance software solutions, gaining understanding of the complex policy systems of the insurance sector.

#### Education

- Web Software Developer (OKJ nmb 54 481 02):
  - Developed skills in various programming languages, web development frameworks, and database management systems.
- Client-Sided Software Developer (OKJ nmb 54-481-02):
  - Gained in-depth client-side programming knowledge.
- Apprenticeship & Mentorship:
  - Participated in an apprenticeship program followed by a mentorship, to further solidifying my software development skills.

# Languages

• English: Proficient

• Hungarian: Native speaker